Stop it! Stop what?
You're talking about me in Morse Code.
But you know what? Joke's on you 'cause l know Morse Code.
Ha!
Yeah, that's what we're doing.
ln our very limited free time and with our very limited budget,
we went and got a nanny, and then we went out and took a class
on a very outmoded and very unnecessary form of communication
Yep, that's exactly what we did.
lt all started when Dwight was tapping his foot against the leg of his desk.
When l asked him to stop, he said,
"l will when you lose the baby weight."
Very well. l must have imagined it. l apologize.
Detonator? Detonator. Where?
Michael !
Jim, are you clicking a detonator?
lt's a pen. Michael, come on.
Get back to work, Dwight. Please.
Fine.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Hey, tap away.
Whoo!
Things with Donna are so. . . They're going great!
l. . . We're just clicking on every level.
Emotionally, and sexually, and orally.
And I am not used to relationships going this well.
l'm actually having trouble focusing on my job.
And I Iike it
Who enjoys the weekends?
Of course. Now the weekend is always great
if you have someone, which l do. l have Donna, she is hot.
She has a Pilates butt.
But we need to find something to do this weekend beside have sex.
Did l say that? Yes, l did.
And the reason you are here is that l need ideas
for things that Donna and l can do on the weekend. So just shout it out.
l have an idea for your weekend. Okay.
Let me go back to my desk right now. Okay.
You get out of here, big dog.
No, no, no, no, you guys sit down. l need ideas.
Stanley got to go.
Yeah, Well, Stanley doesn't help with anything.
Come on, shout them out. Shout them out.
Walk around apple orchards. Oh !
Super romantic. That's fun.
Eel fishing. All right.
Curl up with your favorite DVD.
You and Donna should hit the Poconos.
They have heart-shaped Jacuzzis, room enough for three.
We actually went to the Poconos last Tuesday.
We headed up there, we went to a little Chinese bistro, P. F. Chang's.
Why would you go all the way to the Poconos to P. F. Chang's
when we have the Great Wall in Scranton?
Because when your super-hot girlfriend
says, "l want to go to Mount Pocono,"
you go to Mount Pocono, and you do her.
And we screwed. Whoops! TMl ! (PEOPLE GROANlNG)
Wait, that's crazy far. Are you sure she's not cheating?
You know what, Kelly, this is the real world.
Not, The Real World, Scranton.
Oh, my God, this is super weird.
When Ryan had two girlfriends,
he used to take me to some diner in Hazleton
just so the other girl wouldn't see.
Some diner? lt was the Starlight Diner.
lt's in a Life magazine spread about Americana.
You guys think Donna's cheating on me?
No. Michael, no.
You had a nice meal with your girlfriend in a lovely place.
And sex. We had sex, too. That is right.
Don't make any more of it. How?
How what? How do l not make any more of it?
You could start by concluding this meeting.
All right.
Okay. And she won't say, "l love you."
DWlGHT: Oh, no.
How many dates have you been on?
Nine dates. l said it on the second date.
That seems quick, even for lesbians.
RYAN: Does she keep her phone locked around you, Michael?
Does she watch how much she drinks around you, Michael?
Does she leave the room when she takes phone calls?
Does she keep perfume in her purse? Does she shower before sex?
Does she shower after sex? Does she. . .
Yeah, she does all that.
Sorry, dude. Oh, no, no, no, no.
Michael, do not let your imagination run amok.
Run what? Amok.
lt means don't let your imagination run out of control.
Why didn't you just say that, Pam?
Michael, do not let your imagination run out of control.
Well, that's easy for you to say.
You have a bad imagination, it's stupid.
l live in a fantasy world.
You do?
Yes, Jim, l do.
And l can't stay in a relationship
that is full of lies and deceit.
But you didn't believe any of this was true five minutes ago.
That's what makes it so raw.
Ever since l found out that Donna might be cheating on me,
l have not eaten or slept.
lt's the not knowing, that's what's killing me.
(WHlSPERlNG)
Oh, God, that tickles. What do you. . .
(WHlSPERlNG) l want someone to follow Donna.
l want her tailed.
l need the name of a good private investigator.
(WHlSPERS) l think l've got one for you.
This is you. How much do you charge?
$1 00 a day plus expenses.
l'll give you 50. Money's no object.
Done.
l'm just going to warn you, and l say this to all my clients,
you might not like what l find.
Okay.
And you might not like how l find it.
Of course. Yeah, that's terrible.
Okay, let me get back to you.
Hey, Stanley, one of my clients just called and said that their Sabre printer
started smoking and caught on fire.
My doctor told me to cut out hotdogs. We all got problems.
Hey, Gabe, l need to talk to you about something. lt's really important.
There's no way that you guys have any almond butter, right?
Yeah, l don't know. Look, one of my clients called.
He was in the middle of a big printing job
and the back of the printer started smoking
and then the paper tray caught on fire.
That's weird. l haven't heard of that happening.
l would even settle for apricot preserves.
What are we going to do about this?
l don't know. Call HQ, see if they know anything.
Yeah, that's what l'll do today. All right.
Let me know what they say.
Wow, that dude is good.
What do you mean?
You didn't feel like he was hiding something?
l don't know.
Like he was covering something up?
Maybe.
(DOOR CLOSlNG)
Two years ago, Andy blamed the warehouse
for a late shipment that he forgot to process.
We got yelled at pretty bad, almost lost my job.
Man, l was mad as hell at the time.
But l said, "Darryl, just wait. He's a fool.
"There's going to be an opportunity. Just be patient."
Hey, stranger.
Oh, hi. You work for Michael.
l work with Michael. Right.
Dwight Schrute. Donna, hi.
All cases are solved with logic.
The only logical way to find out if Donna is a cheater is to seduce her,
bring her to orgasm, then call Michael and tell him the sad news.
Wow. lt's a little early for ice cream, don't you think?
lt's never too early for ice cream, Jim.
But we didn't have any ice cream,
so this is mayonnaise and black olives.
Oh ! Oh, my God.
lt's comfort food, all right?
God !
Michael, this whole Donna thing is going to be okay.
You just. . . Stop beating yourself up.
l know. Well, l hope you're right.
We'll see what Dwight says.
Why do we have to see what Dwight says?
Because l have him investigating her.
l'm waiting for a text update.
Michael, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no. Undo that.
Undo that. lt's too late to undo it.
l need to know, otherwise this thing is going to spiral out of amok.
Michael, okay, l'm going to talk straight to you
because l think you need to hear it. Michael. . .
(GRUNTS) This is so disgusting.
Stop eating it. Do you want to be happy?
Look at you. You have a major self-destructive streak in you.
l know. And you. . .
You kind of torpedo every romantic relationship you're in.
That's not true.
You're right. l ruin everything.
And l have known some wonderful women.
Holly, Carole, Jan.
Helene.
Helene?
My mother. Oh !
My mother, Helene.
Oh, yeah. Yes, yes, yes.
All of the greatest loves of my life.
You should stop this. You should call Dwight right now.
(SlGHlNG) All right.
Oh, gosh, we're both going for the same weight at the same time.
You go ahead. Thank you.
lt's all yours. (LAUGHS)
(GRUNTlNG)
(SlGHlNG)
You okay?
Yeah, l'm good.
Hey, you know an exercise for two people that uses the whole body?
(CHUCKLlNG)
Yeah, l think l know what you're talking about.
Tractor pull.
Too bad there's not a tractor here.
(DWlGHT GROANlNG)
(DWlGHT GRUNTlNG)
One thing you need to know about me,
l don't quit until something tears or pops.
(CHUCKLlNG)
You look like you're getting a good workout.
Can l feel your pulse?
(SlGHlNG) Nope, l'm good. Thanks.
Really?
Hey. All right.
Young man, can you wipe down that seat?
Get out of my way.
(LAUGHS) Tomorrow's fertilizer, am l right?
l'm out of here.
Donna, Donna, wait. Please.
l'm sorry, okay?
Listen, we both know why l'm here.
To see you naked
while l'm naked.
You stay away from me or l'm calling security.
Donna, come. . .
(GRUNTlNG)
You're back. What happened?
l pulled muscles in both my thighs. Thanks for asking.
No. What happened with Donna?
Yeah, no. She's not cheating.
Oh, man ! Will you help me work out this knot? Right here.
Put your fingers here. Ugh ! No, no.
Are you sure? l'm positive.
Yeah, here's your expense receipts. Right there.
Who eats eight protein bars?
People who don't trust egg whites.
Okay. Well, l am just glad this is all over.
Oh ! Me, too.
And by the way, l told her not to,
but she's coming over here and she's furious.
What? No, she didn't say that. You're right.
l was paraphrasing.
What she actually said was, "What is with him?
"He is crazy. l'm coming over there to talk to him."
And this was after l had no other recourse
but to tell her and gym security
that you had sent me there to see if she was cheating.
Also, l joined the gym. You'll be billed monthly.
(WHlSPERlNG) l am not paying for that membership.
(MlCHAEL MOANlNG)
(MlCHAEL GRUNTlNG)
Maybe you'd be more comfortable in your own office.
No, l like the attention.
(SlGHlNG)
ls she here yet?
No.
(DOOR OPENlNG)
Wait, yes. That's her?
Yeah.
Mmm-hmm.
Right. Right. Right. Okay, l'll talk to you later.
How could you think l would cheat on you?
l didn't, everybody else here did.
Everybody convinced me that something was up.
They poisoned my mind.
That's pathetic.
(EXHALlNG FORCEFULLY)
Well, no, it's a lie.
That's not what happened.
l just like you. l can't believe l get to be with you.
You work at an adult arcade.
You could have any man you want.
When l tell you l like you, you need to trust me.
Not some freak.
lf you want to dump me, l totally get it.
l told you l like you.
Well, you are bonerific.
(CHUCKLES)
Hey, if l said that we should go away for a couple days, you would. . .
Poop my pants.
Have you ever been to Vero Beach?
Oh, my God, Vero Beach?
No. ls that on the water?
We're going.
We are? Yeah.
What's up? l read your e-mail.
Close the door.
Okay.
l don't have a plan exactly, more of a loose structure.
Gives me freedom to improvise. lt's like jazz.
(SCATTlNG)
♪ Andy don't mess with me ♪
l'll figure something out.
Some freaky stuff going on.
l was walking by Gabe and l heard some things.
Such as?
lt was kind of mumbled. l don't know.
The only thing l could make out clearly was, "Andy, problem, eliminate."
Something. l don't know what it meant.
What? You don't know what it meant?
How about, "Andy is a problem and we must eliminate him."
Oh ! l hadn't even thought of that.
(LAUGHlNG) Yeah.
(EXCLAlMlNG)
Oh, hey, l love your earrings.
Thank you.
Did Michael get them for you?
No, l bought them myself.
Where?
(STAMMERS) Steamtown Mall.
Claire's? Zales? Ricky's? Earrings, Earrings, Earrings?
Fancy Girl? Platinum Cat?
Where?
You know, l actually got them in Philadelphia.
ln a mall down there.
Franklin Mills?
King of Prussia? Springfield? Governor's Place?
Franklin Mills.
What? Hmm.
Oh !
lt's probably nothing.
Okay, heart-shaped jewelry is not something that a woman buys for herself,
a man definitely bought it for her recently,
and it wasn't Michael.
Wait, so you like heart-shaped jewelry, though, right?
No.
Except for the pendant that you bought me.
Which l love.
Psst!
Creed's head of Quality Assurance,
so he'd definitely be wrapped up in this.
So there l am minding my own business,
and Darnell offers me three bucks.
All l've got to do is walk by Andy and go like this.
Darnell's a chump. l would've done it for anything.
l've done a lot more for a lot less.
PAM: So, it turns out Donna and I have a Facebook friend of a friend in common,
so l was able to see some of her pictures online.
This was taken two weeks ago.
And this was taken the same night.
This photo was taken this morning.
lt's Cece.
She's never going to do anything wrong.
lsn't that something? Wow. That's exciting.
Hey, Michael. Hey.
Sorry to interrupt you.
l actually have something very important to talk to you about.
Well, it can wait. Business related.
lt can wait. l lied, it's personal.
lt's about me and Jim, we're. . .
(STAMMERS) You're the only person l can talk to.
Jim is her husband. Oh.
PAM: And. . . And they're having problems. . .
No, no, we're not. . . . . .and so she comes to me.
We're not having problems, but it is personal.
And l was. . . ln bed.
(CLlCKlNG TONGUE)
Yes, yes, l desperately want to speak with you
about my sex life with Jim. (MlCHAEL CLEARlNG THROAT)
Oh, my God, look at how cheap street-level rooms are.
Am l the only person who enjoys people-watching?
l need you to sign this!
So bad ! Okay, weirdo.
l love. . . This idea is neat.
l've never been. Yeah.
lt sounds lovely.
Yeah, l think it'll be a nice trip. We're going to get a lot done.
You're going to want to look at the date on that.
Oh ! Wow. Look at golfing.
Are you a golfer?
l am, but l gave my clubs away.
Swear too much.
(BOTH LAUGHlNG)
Hey, you okay?
Yeah, l just remembered that l have to go to the bathroom.
Pam? Absolutely.
Look, l'm not down anymore, so if the guys start making fun of you,
you've just gotta stand up for yourself.
l know. lt's just, l'm scared. . . ANDY: l got your text.
lt said, "91 1 ."
Glen, could you excuse us?
lt's bad. What's bad?
lt's real bad.
Still no plan.
Oh, God. lt's getting bigger.
l might have to go public here, but no one's going to believe me. Uh. . .
l need proof. l need, like, a printer to catch on fire.
l can videotape it. Yeah.
There it is.
There what is?
What?
Who the hell is this? Who is this guy?
l don't know who it is. God !
Lowest of the low, that guy.
Just a notch above Toby.
You know what? What?
l'm going to kill him. No, l'm not. l feel. . . No.
l'm not going to kill him.
You just have to go in there. You have to hear it from her.
l have to hear it from her. But you have to settle down first.
l need to have her tell me herself. Okay.
Okay. Right?
Yes. l need to have her say. . .
l need to say, "What the hell is that? Calm down first.
"What the hell is that?" Hey, look at this.
Look at this baby picture.
(GRUNTlNG) Oh, God, no. Oh, my God.
Hi, Michael.
Hi, Michael. Okay.
Okay.
l talked to corporate. Turns out there have been 1 2 reports of faulty printers.
Out of 400,000.
We've investigated. Every time it's been user error.
They block the vents or something, l don't know.
That's why we have the fine print.
Thank you for bringing this to our attention.
So, l'd like to reward you for that.
That's good for five bucks at Dunkin' Donuts. Any Dunkin' Donuts.
Oh.
You know what? We should really do something fun this week.
Yeah. Wouldn't that be fun?
Yeah.
How about Thursday?
Thursday works, yeah.
What do you want to do? l can't do it Thursday, book club.
How about Friday?
Oh ! Friday doesn't work.
Oh, really? 'Cause l was thinking we could go to this concert.
Spice Girls are opening for Weird Al. Front row.
Be a great, great concert.
Shoot. l'm working.
Oh ! Okay, well, maybe l should stop by.
Well, won't you be at the concert?
Nope, that's Tuesday.
Well, l can make it on Tuesday.
You're cheating.
You're cheating on me.
(CLlCKlNG TONGUE) How do you know?
Pam told me.
(GASPS) Did she see me?
Nice effort.
We're printing on 24-pound premium stock paper,
approximately 300 sheets in. So far no signs of distress.
You haven't even introduced yourself. Right.
My name is Andrew Baines Bernard and if you're watching this,
it's because I've turned state's witness, because I'm in danger,
because I know too much.
You should talk in a higher voice
'cause the camera makes you sound weird.
Higher, okay?
Recently certain events have come to my attention...
Higher. Make it higher?
Okay. (lN HlGH PlTCHED TONE) I have come to the concIusion that the Sabre Corporation...
One more, yeah.
(lN SQUEAKY TONE) ...may be overlooking certain safety regulations.
At the danger...
(lN NORMAL VOlCE) It's smoking.
l knew it!
This. . . We are blowing the roof off!
Blowing the roof off!
Nice, nice.
This is my partner, Darryl Philbin.
He's been my partner through this entire thing.
l don't want to prank anymore.
Things get real. lt's not funny.
l'm just going to be good. Stay in my room,
go to church, try to do one nice thing per day.
l do not want to prank anymore.
Who is he?
Wait, what do you mean? The other man.
Who's the guy? Who is it?
lt's you. l'm married.
l'm the mistress?
Okay, everybody, let's take this next hill !
Excuse me. Yeah, I'd appreciate it if you'd just let me run this.
You know what? You had your chance, you're no leader.
Up, out of your seat! Let's blast! Don't Iisten to him.
We're approaching a cool-down, down a gentle hill.
No! The hill's a trap. Let's take the dirt road off to the side.
No, guys, no. We're just cooling down.
lf they catch us, they will rape us.
Go for the cliff. And three, two, one, jump!
No! You're dead, you're dead, you're dead. Good jump.
You're barely alive. Okay, now, nice cool-down.
Check your pulse rate.